{
    "subject": "resource/Devil_May_Cry_3:_Dante's_Awakening",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "Xbox 360",
    "human_readable": "Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening was released on Xbox 360 platforms.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9503450393676758,
            "question": "On which gaming platform was Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9030789136886597,
            "question": "When was Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8286914229393005,
            "question": "Is Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening available on PC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6030884385108948,
            "question": "Who developed Devil May Cry 3?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45545655488967896,
            "question": "Is there a sequel to Devil May Cry 3?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4393942356109619,
            "question": "Who is the main character in Devil May Cry 3?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40644654631614685,
            "question": "What is the theme of Devil May Cry 3?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39300480484962463,
            "question": "What genre is Devil May Cry 3 classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38117238879203796,
            "question": "What are some key gameplay features of Devil May Cry 3?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05763636529445648,
            "question": "What is the full title of the game?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening was released on Xbox 360 platforms.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4176_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key gameplay features of Devil May Cry 3?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4176_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Devil May Cry 3 classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4176_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the theme of Devil May Cry 3?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4176_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4176_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The information from the documents indicates that Devil May Cry 3: Dante\u2019s Awakening was released for various platforms, including the Xbox 360. Specifically, in document 87.txt and document 57.txt, it is mentioned that the game will be available on Xbox 360 as part of the Devil May Cry HD Collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}